<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal on Ramesh&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://RameshArvind.github.io/tags/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal on Ramesh&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 10:25:40 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://RameshArvind.github.io/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Got Into Computer Programming</title>
      <link>http://RameshArvind.github.io/posts/personal/why-i-got-into-cs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 10:25:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://RameshArvind.github.io/posts/personal/why-i-got-into-cs/</guid>
      <description>This dates back to when I was in high school around start of my 10th grade. I got access to internet for the first time in my life 1.
Up until this point, my only interactions with a computer was purely as a device for gaming. I used to spend a disproportionate of time playing games 2.
I made an account on facebook and played the games on it cause it was all the rage at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Georgia Tech&#39;s OMSCS Program</title>
      <link>http://RameshArvind.github.io/posts/personal/what-is-omscs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 07:31:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://RameshArvind.github.io/posts/personal/what-is-omscs/</guid>
      <description>OMSCS is Georgia Tech&amp;rsquo;s Online Master&amp;rsquo;s Program in Computer Science. It is run fully online, generally taken up by working professionals.
I enrolled into the program in Fall Semester (September - December) of 2018 thus completing one semester at the time of writing.
Before I considered OMSCS I originally intended to apply to on-campus programs in the US, but I ended up skipping out multiple times
 First when my peers applied right out of their undergraduate program When my co-workers applied first year into their career and when they applied second year into their career  Each time I kept thinking &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not going to procrastinate this year and apply&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>http://RameshArvind.github.io/posts/personal/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 04:41:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://RameshArvind.github.io/posts/personal/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Why even blog? So then, this is probably going to be a pretty boring intro to what I&amp;rsquo;m trying to get at by blogging.
I spend a lot time on the internet, it&amp;rsquo;s actually more surprising when I don&amp;rsquo;t find myself on it. I&amp;rsquo;m easily distracted when I&amp;rsquo;m trying to be productive and have a hard time trying to focus. There are specific things I&amp;rsquo;d like to achieve by blogging</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>